Denenberg, Tia Schneider Arbitration Files 6275
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Newsday, Inc. and Nassau County Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union, Local 406 Agreement, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- New York City and AFSCME, Council 37 Labor Relations Order No. 83/1, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  July 15
- NYC & NYS Nurses Assn. & NYC Health & Hospitals Corp., 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- New York Health and Hospitals corporation, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- New York City of and NYC Health and Hospitals Corporation and New York State Nurses Assoc., 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- City of New York and related public employers and Social Service Employers Union Local 371 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- New York, State of and United University Professions, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- NYS Thruway Auth. And NYS TEIBT (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Onteora School District and Onteora Non-Teaching Employees Assn., 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Paid Prescriptions, Inc. and United Storeworkers Union, 1979-1981 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Pathmark (Supermarkets General Corp.) and United food & Commercial Wkrs Agreement, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Pearl River BOE and Pearl Rivers Tchrs. Assn., 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- PA & AFSCME Agreement, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- PA & AFSCME, council 13 Master Memorandum (Box 30, Folder 30)
- PA & AFSCME, Council 13 Master Agreement, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- PA and AFSCME, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Council 13, 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- PA and AFSCME, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- PA, comm. Of & PSSU, Local 668 & PESEA, Local 675, 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Pennsylvania Power Company and IBEW, Local Union 272, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Penntech Papers, Inc. and UPIU, Local 701, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania - Independent State Stores Union Liquor Store Managers Unit, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- PA and PA Nurses Assoc. Memorandum of Understanding & Agreement, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- PA & PA State Educ. Assoc., 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- PA and PSSU, PESEA, 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Plainedge Union Free School District and Plainedge Federation of Teachers, 1977-1980 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Portsmouth Naval Shipyard and Federal employees Metal Trades Council, 1977-1984 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Poughkeepsie, City of and Fire Fighters, Local 596, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Poughkeepsie, City of and fire Fighters, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Prestolite Battery Company Div. (Eltra corp,) and USA, Local 6130, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Public Service Electric & Gas company and IBEW, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Putnam county and NYS Nurses Assn., 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Quinnipiac College and Quinnipiac Faculty Fed., Local 3394, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- R&H Manufacturing, Inc. & Int'l Bro. of Boilermakers, Etc., Local 677 Agreement, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Rye Neck Union Free School District and Rye Neck teachers Assoc., 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Schoeller Tech. Papers., Inc. and UPIU Local 1066, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- Septa and Transport Workers union of Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- social Security Adminis. & AFGE (AFL-CIO), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 52)
- Social Security Administration and AFGE, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- Spackenkill Union Free School District and Spackenkill Teachers Assn. (Box 30, Folder 54)
- Sperry Div. of Sperry Rand and IUERMW, AFL-CIO, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 55)
- Springfield Twp SD + Springfield Tchrs Assoc.; Portsmouth Naval Shipyard + FEMT Council, AFL-CIO, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 56)
- The Stanley Works - Local No. 1433 IAMAW (Box 30, Folder 57)
- Sterling Drug, Inc. and Intern'l chemical workers, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 58)
- Three Village Central School District and Three Village Teachers Assn., 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 59)
- Various Agreements, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  Roncalli Health Center - Dist. 1199; New Jersey Water Company Haddon District - IBFO Local 473 AFL-CIO; Sheriff's Department Info; Chirs - Craft Industrial Products, Inc. - URCLPWA, Local 104
- Various Labor Agreements, 1960-1980 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  Columbia Box Board Mills, Inc., Chatham, NY - International Brotherhood of Paper Makers; The Columbia Corporation Chatham, NY - UPP (AFL-CIO) Chatham Local 471; The Columbia corporation Chatham, New York - UPIU (AFL-CIO) Chatham Local 471
- NYS Division of Parole & PEF, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- NYS Office of Mental Health Rockland Psychiatric Center & Public Employees Federation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- PEF and NYS, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  Direct Linda OER
- State of NY & PEF, AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  State Exhibits, Briefs, Testimony
- State of NY & PEF, AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- State of New York (DOT) & Public Employees Federation, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- State of NY and PEF, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- State of New York (DOT) & Public Employees Federation, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- NYS (SUNY Buffalo) & UUP, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Rensselaer county & Rensselaer CTY Dep Sheriffs' Assn. NYSPERB, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- NYS (SUNY) and PEF, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- NYS (SUNY) & PEF, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- NYS (SUNY) & PEF, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Stamford Board of Education Educational Assistants of Stamford Associates, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Stella D'Oro Transcripts (Disks Included) (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Stella D'Oro and BCTWU, Local 50 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- United Airlines and IAMAW Discharge of Kevin Wilson for Rule 2, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Waterford-Half Moon CSD and Waterford Teachers Association, NYSPERB (Box 32, Folder 11)
- AT&T & CWA VTP Disputes, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- AT&T and CWA VTP Disputes (Box 33, Folder 2)
- AT&T and CWA VTP Disputes Joint Ex #5-8 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- AT&T and CWA VTP Disputes, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- AT&T & CWA VTP Disputes, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- NYC Board of Education and United Federation of Teachers, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- NYC Board of Education and United Federation of Teachers, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- State of NY Banking Dept. & PEF, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Rensselaer CTY & Rensselaer CTY Sheriff's Dept. and CSEA, Inc., 2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- American Airlines and APFA, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Bell Atlantic - NJ and IBEW Local 827, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Bell Atlantic - NJ & IBEW 827, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Center for Optimum Care and UFCW371, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- HNS Management Co. & ATU Local 281, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- New York City Dept. of environmental Protection and AFSCME,, DC 37, Local 375, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- HNS Management Co.& ATU Local 281, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Quay International and UPIU Local 118 FMCS Case No. 99-02169, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- NYC and Teamsters Local 237, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Plattsburgh and AFSCME Co. 66, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Rhinebeck Central School District and Steven Grim, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Soundview Nursing Home & UFCW, Local 371, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Actors' Equity Association and Michael Metts, As Producer of Shering/Key National Meeting, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Bell Atlantic and IBEW Local 827, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Brinkman Instruments and Local 804, IBT, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Columbia-Greene Community College and AFSCME Council 66, Local 3662, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- International Paper and Pace Local 254, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Pine Bush Central School District - Pine Bush Teachers' Assoc., 1999 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Presidential Emergency Board 224:Long Island Railroad and UTU, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Presidential Emergency Board 224: Long Island Railroad and UTU, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Presidential Emergency board 224, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- PEB 223, Hearing Exhibits (Box 35, Folder 4)
- PEB 223, LIRR Post Hearing Submission in Lieu of Brief (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Presidential Emergency Board 224: Long Island Railroad and UTU, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- PEB Health Insurance Plans 224 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Kennedy Valve & UE, Local 329 FMCS Elmira D. Deats - Discipline, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- NJ Bell Telephone and IBEW Local 827, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Nestle Food Company and BCTWU, Local 50, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- NJ Bell and IBEW Award. 5-day suspension Joseph T Capasso (Box 36, Folder 4)
- NYS (Health) & PEF, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- NYS (DFY) and PEF, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Niagara Mohawk & IBEW Co. U-11Discharge of P. Rando, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Nimo ( Rando - Discharge), 1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Nimo Rando (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Nimo (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Packaging Corp. and UPIU, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Arlington Central School District & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Arlington Central School district & Anthony & Laura Ragaglia, as parents of AR Special Education Case (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Niskayuna Central School District sp. Ed., 99-10-2-2-5 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Brendan Cosgrove and the Niskayuna Central School District (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Niskayuna Central School District sp. Ed., 99-10-2-2-5 Direct Exhibits (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Niskayuna Schools Petitioner's Memorandum of Law (Ritzberg - Young, Sommer) (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Niskayuna and Brendan Cosgrove Memo of Law and cites (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Niskayuna Central School district Transcripts Sp. Ed. (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Niskayuna Central School districts Sp. Ed. Transcripts (Box 38, Folder 7)
- champion international & UPIU Termination Leo Lawler, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Hartford Board of Ed and HFT, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- county of Clinton & CSEA NY PERB, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Dean Foods & ACTWU, Local 1822, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Laidlaw Transit Inc. & IBT Local 182A, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- NYS & PEF, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- NYS Division of Parole & PEF, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- NYS and PEF Frank Farahmond Creedmore, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Steelwater School & CSEA, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Sweet Life Foods & Teamsters Suspension of R. Dellaripa, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Triborough Bridge + BTOBA, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Triborough Bridge + BTOBA, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Triborough Bridge + BTOBA, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Agreements, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Lucent Technologies - IBEW; Lucent Technologies - IBEW(2); AT&T Corp. - Communications Workers of America; Bell Atlantic- New Jersey, Inc. - Bell Atlantic-Network Services, Inc.; The University of Connecticut Health center - University Health Professionals Local 3837 AFT/CFEPE/AFL-CIO
- Agreements - Effective 1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  State of New York - United University Professions; State of New York - United University Professions(2); CSEA, Inc. Local 1000 AFCMS, AFL-CIO - The State of New York; The State of New York - The Public employees Federation, AFL-CIO; The State of New York - The Public employees Federation, AFL-CIO(2); The State of New York - The Public employees Federation, AFL-CIO(3); The State of New York - The Public employees Federation, AFL-CIO(4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Agreements - Effective 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  Local 827 IBEW, AFL-CIO - Verizon NJ Inc., Verizon Services Corp., Organization of Vice President and Comptroller and General Departments and Plant and Engineering Department - Plant Engineering Departments; Agreement and Rules Governing Employment Under the Equity/League Production Contract (Actor's Equity Association); Local 827 IBEW, AFL-CIO - Verizon NJ Inc., and Verizon Services Corp., Organization of Vice President and Comptroller and General Departments and Plant and Engineering Departments; Agreement and Rules Governing employment Under the Off Broadway Agreement (Actor's Equity Association)
- Agreements - Effective 2000-2003 (Box 40, Folder 4)